This is UCCA's "Yukai de Funa Showroom"!
Hello everyone, we are UCCA!
Thank you for joining us today!
Today's show will be brought to you by
me, Akane Sora!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching the 128th episode
of "Ukka no Yaikai"
Are you watching?
Yes, we are
Oh, there are a lot of our logos.
There are the ones I drew.
Everyone, if you are changing your
clothes, if you are doing something
different, please make it ours.
Please make it U.
Please.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward
to it.
Thank you very much.
You're telling me to try something on.
Shall we introduce ourselves along with
the introduction?
Yes, please.
I'm the owner, Aoi Ruri. Nice to meet
you.
I think this is probably a maid.
It looks like something you'd wear on
Halloween.
Oh, it does!
It does, doesn't it?
It's like a long skirt.
Ruru-chan, please wear it.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, it's Maa-chan's turn.
What's this?
It looks like a rabbit.
It's cute.
Please wear it.
It's colored with hair.
That's right.
Please wear it.
Next, I will introduce you to my ears.
What is this?
It's not a cell phone.
I'm Akane Sato, who has warm ears.
Please.
It's cute.
It's warm.
So, I made clothes with the original
avatar.
Did you get it?
There are a lot of people who are
commenting right now, but if you gift it
in this room, the original avatar will
be presented, so please try to get it.
Do you get other members' icons?
There was a person who gave it to me
earlier.
Really?
GingaGuitar-san, Chaiin-san, Sora-san,
Ruri-san, and Sasaki-san.
Ginga-san is also cute.
If you want to get it, please give it to
me.
Please.
It's time to spread the word.
We will post the announcement on X now.
Please retweet it.
We are wearing cute clothes today.
The song is also cute.
Let's do a cute pose.
Cute pose?
Let's say that we can see cute members
after this.
Is the comment okay?
Please leave a comment.
If you get it, we will post it.
I don't think we can do cute poses.
It doesn't look good on you.
It doesn't look good on me.
I can do it.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Let's pose.
5,4,3,2,1
Oh, it's cute.
Where is it?
Today?
I'm looking for you.
Thank you.
So, I'm going to post an announcement on
X right now, so please retweet it.
It's okay to like it, but please retweet
it.
Please.
Yes.
So, I'm going to go to the recording
studio.
First of all, this corner.
"Yukai de FUNA 15 minutes update"
So, I'm going to talk about the recent
events of "Yukai de FUNA" freely.
"Ukka" is a group that protects time.
Yes.
So, in exactly 15 minutes, I will talk
about the events of the group and the
individual events.
After 15 minutes, it will end no matter
how much I talk about it.
I can't listen to that story anymore.
I see.
That's a good story.
I can't listen to it for the rest of my
life.
I can't listen to it.
I want to say it.
I can't talk about it wherever I go.
I understand.
So, everyone, is it okay?
From now on.
How many minutes?
5 minutes.
So, I'm going to start now.
Ready.
Start.
Yes.
So, I think I'll talk about the recent
events of the group.
First of all, the lyric video of the
song "TOUMEI" that is playing now has
been released.
Yes.
Let's listen to the sound.
"TOUMEI"
"TOUDE SAGETSU"
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This song has a lot of solo parts,
right?
That's right.
There's no chorus, right?
Yes.
It's a professional song.
Thank you very much.
The lyric video of this song has been
released.
This time, rather than members coming
out,
It's an illustration.
Like an illustration of being in love.
Even if you have a friend who doesn't
like idols,
This is a little easy to recommend.
That's right.
Like, the art is cool, the movements are
good.
We would like you to talk about the
story.
I hope you can listen to it.
That's it now.
The top of the secret expo.
It's an ending theme, so I hope everyone
will listen to it a lot.
It's tomorrow, isn't it?
It's Thursday.
It's Thursday, so everyone, please watch
it until the end and listen to this
song.
And if you watch the lyric video, please
give it a high rating and comment.
Please.
And if you like, please share it on
Twitter.
I'd be happy if you could share it on X
and post it a lot.
If you're watching this right now,
please.
Please.
I'd be happy if you could add a comment
like, "I like this part."
Please.
And the performance of "Wookka the
Journey Beginner's Tour 2024 Spring Hop
Step Jump"
will be held on May 12th in Osaka
and on May 10th in Tokyo.
It was held in Kanagawa on the 19th.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
It's already over twice.
It's quick.
It's fast.
How was it?
Osaka Park.
First of all.
Do you remember?
I don't remember much.
It's a pattern I remember from the
beginning.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Did you get banana juice at Osaka Park?
It doesn't matter, but it's delicious.
That's right.
I did it at the name of the venue called
Banana Hall.
I came because it seems that the banana
juice is famous.
I think that the people who care about
turban are drinking it.
Yes.
The drinks came after this live.
I went over to see what was the problem.
Moa-chan was the soloist for Osaka,
right? That's right.
I was the soloist for Osaka.
I want you to listen to this. I didn't
tell you this, right?
When Osaka was over, I was like "Osaki?"
I didn't tell you that I was coming to
Osaka.
I didn't tell you.
After that, I couldn't go to the
concert, so I was kicked out of the
concert.
I was kicked out?
Yes, I was kicked out of the concert.
I don't know how to say it.
Ballad.
It's rare for a ballad singer to sing
alone as a one-man band.
So I was a little nervous at the time of
the solo concert.
I was nervous, but I had a lot of fun.
That's good.
I'm sorry to say that.
I really like your back voice, so I
listened to it a lot.
Did you fall in love with it?
I didn't fall in love with it, but I
thought I liked it.
I see. Thank you.
Don't get too excited.
But it's all over here.
That's right.
It was the first time.
I was really nervous.
I didn't know what it would feel like.
I was very nervous.
When Ruri was singing, I was the fourth
person.
There are about four performances.
Ruri, you're nervous.
Ruri, do your best.
I was watching the video.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous.
It's a little surprising.
The lyrics are wrong.
She says, "I cut off the sky in Tokyo
and I hope you'll do the same"
The chorus is the worst.
Ruri's high-profile pitch was very
difficult.
But it was fun.
I'm glad you got the solo at the end of
the concert.
The solo is lapped in steps, so what
happens to the jump?
You'll realize that.
What will happen?
At the end.
Right.
I can't.
So maybe something will change.
And the outfit just now is the last one.
I wonder what it will be like.
"Journey Begins" will be held at Miyagi
Sendai Derby on Sunday, May 26th at
HOPPE STEP JUMP SPRING.
This is the last step performance.
As I said, there are two more solo
performances left.
I'm not sure which one will be the best.
Don't say it.
Don't say it even if you hear it
somewhere.
I want you to look forward to which one
will be the best.
HOPPE STEP JUMP will be held on
Wednesday, May 26th at HOPPE STEP JUMP
SPRING.
The costumes may have changed.
The song may have changed.
What will it be like?
By the way, we are doing a lesson.
It may be like that.
That's right.
I want to show you.
Please let us do it.
Please come to the concert.
We are waiting for you.
We are talking about KANAGAWA.
KAWASAKI.
Right.
KAWASAKI SPELNOVA.
KAWASAKI is the most popular.
It was very hot.
It was hot.
The accumulation of the past came to me.
I talked about my impressions.
What was your impression?
I heard your impressions.
When I talk, my voice goes up a little.
YU-CHAN asked me if I was crying.
I didn't cry.
I didn't cry at all.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were going to cry.
I thought I was going to cry.
I didn't cry at all.
My voice went up.
KAWASAKI was amazing.
I cried.
Did you cry?
That's right.
Isn't it often to see glitter?
The feeling for glitter is good.
Wow.
That's right.
Iret's osoby was the best Snow provoc un
before the refreshing.
My cries.
I was passed.
Someone else.
I win.
Wow.
I know.
I understood.
Someone else.
I won.
Something.
You seem to get some sun.
Tell me.
Everyone may be pray a door at last.
We look forward.
Connection.
It's a little個 리뷰 with Akira Oye.
On May 11th, we were able to perform in
Marloupe in Osaka. Thank you very much.
It's been a while since we performed in
Osaka.
We were asked to perform on the main
stage.
It was really exciting.
It was amazing.
The first song was called "Everybody
Wannabe".
It was a really exciting song.
From then on, we were really excited.
It's been a while since we performed on
the main stage.
We performed "Wonder Little Love" and
"Killer Lips" on the main stage.
It was really fun.
It was our first time performing on
"Killer Lips", right?
That's right.
I think we were able to perform on
various stages.
On the main stage.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please come to Osaka again.
We will come to Osaka again.
Thank you very much.
Is this the end of the group
performance?
That's right.
Do you have any personal stories?
Can I talk about it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What?
The other day, I performed on "Cal
Comedy Red", which was held at Tokyo
Culture Culture.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
It was my first performance.
Yes.
I was selected for the comedy stage.
Everyone, I sold out.
That's right.
I was a member of Team A.
I sold out the ticket.
I also sold out the Akusta.
That's amazing.
I wanted to tell you that I was
grateful.
Thank you very much.
Did everyone come?
It was us.
I'm sorry.
We were bold enough to invite you.
It's okay.
Then I came in.
Did everyone come?
They all went.
It was everyone.
Everyone came.
Oh, everyone came.
I had a plan.
What if I couldn't make it?
What's that?
Oh.
Rehearsal.
Oh, the comedy?
Comedy.
Comedy also came out in the middle.
I didn't get to go.
But sorry.
I don't care at all.
If you say this, this is my schedule.
I saw Saya's stage schedule.
I thought it would be here, and I was
going in.
There was a photo shoot not there.
I'm sorry.
The plan.
I don't care at all.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Well,
I'll tell you after the show.
There's an hour and a half of one stage.
We're going to do four of them.
Yes.
The four of them are all...
It's a story of putting a foreshadowing
on it and collecting it at the end.
Each one of them has a different role.
The first one is a baby role.
The second one is an extension role.
An extension role in kindergarten.
The third one is a tomato role.
Tomato?
It's the role of a carotene component of
a tomato.
At the end,
It was the role of an old woman.
There were a lot of things like that.
We used different voices.
I see.
That's why I turned off my voice.
That's why.
I was screaming.
I turned off my voice.
The hospital is good.
I was really worried.
I thought you were going to DM me.
Are you okay?
I'm not going to see you.
I was about to cry.
My voice didn't come out.
After the training,
When I went to the lesson,
I asked Yuu.
I asked you a space delivery.
Is your voice okay?
Did you have a bad radio wave?
It didn't come out.
I was right there.
Your voice is talking.
But you can't hear it.
I was very anxious, but I was able to
finish it without any problems.
Thank you for saying that it was fun.
There were a lot of rehearsals and
performances.
Thank you very much.
If I have a chance again,
Next time...
Oh, that's right.
Next time, I'm going to have a live
concert.
It's in July.
I still have tickets for that.
Please check it out.
I would be happy if you could come.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Is there anything you want to say?
I ran into Sora-chan in the wild.
This is a small story.
Which one is it?
When I went to see the movie...
I went to see the movie with Rishi-chan.
When I went to see the movie, I looked
back and saw Sora-chan.
I was surprised.
That's amazing.
She was an innocent Sora-chan.
It was empty today.
When I went to the showroom, I thought
I'd have a break.
But I stopped shopping a while ago.
I thought I'd go to see the movie.
I went to the movie theater.
I were there first.
I was filmed in the back.
I was shooting at the corner.
It's started...
It's pretty dark.
Do you know?
It gets dark once and then it gets dark
twice.
When it gets dark once, someone comes in
front of me and says,
"Oh, a young girl is coming."
Do you want me to tell you a story?
It's called "Trapezium."
It's a novel by Takayama, a former
Nogizaka fan.
I went to see it, so I thought, "Is she
a Nogizaka fan?"
But it was dark, so I couldn't see her.
And then one of them came out.
I was like, "No!"
The person in front of me came out.
I thought there were people who came out
during the performance.
Because of various reasons, right?
It got brighter.
The person in front of me came out.
I thought I met the person in front of
me.
I wanted to make my eyes wide open.
I want to talk to you.
I wonder what it is.
That's all for Yuka and Yuna's 15-minute
emergency report.
Thank you, Sorashino-san.
Thank you.
I'm worried.
I'm worried I'm sending you a tower in
song.
Thank you.
So we're going to move on to the next
event.
The next corner is this one.
Yuka and Yuna's proud girlfriend.
We three are the girlfriend of the
listener.
It was a long time ago.
Yes, I already put it on.
We're already dating.
From now on, let's answer various
questions as a proud girlfriend.
In the final vote, we will decide who is
the most proud girlfriend.
Billy will live as a girlfriend who
cannot be proud for a while.
If you give me a warning, I can't be
proud.
If you see this, one of you will be
recognized as a girlfriend who cannot be
proud.
Next time, you will be told.
I can't be proud.
No.
I want to be proud.
There is a topic, so please announce it.
Here is the first topic.
Ta-da.
A word to encourage a tired boyfriend.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
A word to encourage a tired boyfriend.
I will write it on the flip and announce
it.
Yes.
What is it?
I'm really tired.
I'm tired too.
I'm lost.
When we met, the staff asked me what
kind of transformation I was good at.
I'm good at it.
You're working hard.
That's right.
It's difficult.
I don't know what to say.
I'm tired and lonely.
I wrote it down.
Is it okay?
Let's go.
Please say a word to encourage your
boyfriend who is tired.
You did your best today.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's really good.
If you don't want to say it, I'll say
it.
Thank you.
Self-charge.
Are you tired?
I'm a little tired.
You did your best today.
Self-charge.
Thank you.
I see.
This is attached.
Moa, are you done?
Please shake this.
This is really bad.
Please say a word to encourage your
boyfriend who is tired.
Look at me.
When you see me, you will be healed.
I see.
I can't do it by myself.
I got pinched.
So, you say you want to be healed by
Moa.
She is cute.
Moa, look at this way.
Please look at me.
Why are you looking at me?
You are cute.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is different from other people.
It's fun to draw.
I finished drawing.
Someone, please draw.
Please say a word to your boyfriend who
is tired.
Good luck.
Let's go to ramen.
You look like Moa.
Men love ramen.
That's true.
Men want ramen when they are tired.
I invited you to ramen.
That's good.
We have three people here.
Let's vote.
Let's decide who is good.
Thank you.
If you like Ruri, please vote for No.1.
If you like Moa, please vote for No.2.
If you like Akane, please vote for No.3.
Let's start voting.
Everyone, please vote.
Which one do you think is the best?
It's important to get 1 vote each,
right?
That's right.
The one with the most votes will be the
winner.
Or the one with the most votes will be
the winner.
In total?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
The winner is...
Who will it be?
Oh, it's me! Yay!
So, my Yuki's "Let's go eat ramen" is 1
second!
Yay! 1 win!
Wow, that's hard!
Let's ask Yuki for a reason.
Sure. Why?
It's pretty important, right?
Let's learn from here.
Let's study.
What did you like?
I'll write down what I liked.
Food is good.
Ramen is popular.
Ramen.
I want to eat ramen.
Buri, you're spartan.
Why?
It's self-charge.
It's self-charge, but I'm kind.
It would have been better if it was Buri
Charge.
I see.
You need to be kind.
Self-charge is not good.
Self-charge is bad.
It's important to be specific.
I see.
I didn't write anything.
Look at me.
It's long.
No way.
I see. You have a strong appetite, so
you shouldn't eat too much.
I see. I've learned a lot.
Thank you.
Let's move on to the next one.
The second one is this one.
Your boyfriend's date plan for his
birthday.
What does this have to do with your
boyfriend's blood type?
I thought about it, but I wanted to say
something that was more in the schedule.
Ah, that's true.
Can I decide that too?
No, no, no.
What is it? It's hard.
Doesn't it depend on whether it's summer
or winter?
It doesn't.
It doesn't depend on whether it's summer
or winter, right?
Oh, Kurisu, it's your turn.
It's my turn.
Thank you.
I'm doing a project right now, and I'm
using the voting function, so please
watch it.
Please.
What should I do?
What is it?
It's hard.
Wait, wait, wait.
Your boyfriend's date plan for his
birthday.
Date plan, right?
I see.
Wow...
This is difficult.
I don't know. What should I do?
This is hard.
I know it's a secret, but what should I
do?
I only cry once a year, so I want to
take good care of it.
That's true.
What is it? Wait, wait.
For the time being...
Well...
It's difficult.
Are they happy?
First of all.
I wonder if they are happy.
Aren't you all curious?
Where do you want to go?
I'm about to finish.
You're so fast.
It's difficult.
I'll draw a little more.
Is this my style?
Yes, please.
Okay, I'm done.
Okay, please announce the answer.
I'm a type A boyfriend.
I can sleep in a bed.
I wake up at 8:00.
I eat ramen for breakfast at 8:30.
I leave at 12:00.
I go to the zoo at 14:00.
I don't do self-charge.
You go to the zoo.
I eat dinner at 18:00.
I eat ramen for dinner at 12:00.
I can sleep in a bed.
You are a type A boyfriend.
Please study hard.
What do you think?
You are like a baby.
You are not like me.
I did it like this.
I put ramen noodles in my favorite
ramen.
I think so.
I'm going to eat ramen.
You look like Moa-chan.
I don't like ramen in the morning.
You don't like it in the morning, do
you?
I don't like it.
I think everyone likes it.
I'm curious.
Is it a point?
If it's the other way around, you might
get angry if you fill in the schedule,
but if it's the good way, it's just the
right amount.
Certainly, I'm okay with filling in the
schedule.
Isn't it a little less?
I don't know what to do.
It's my turn.
I'll put in my own time.
I really don't know.
What should I do?
By the way, my hairstyle is the first
hairstyle that everyone loves.
You can do this, right?
I'm always taking my ears off.
It's a little dangerous.
It's a little embarrassing.
Let's see...
I'll explain it with my mouth.
It's decided.
First of all, I'll call Reiji for the
time being.
Reiji is cute.
I'll call Reiji for the time being and
say congratulations.
Next, let's get together at around
13:00.
Slowly.
I'm not good at morning, so I'll do it
together.
Nice.
Let's get together and go on a trip by
train or car.
Nice.
We can drive.
That's a good idea.
It's paper.
It's paper, so please put on your
helmets.
We'll go on a trip by train or car.
I'll go home on the day after tomorrow.
I'll go home.
I'll take a bath.
I can sleep.
I'll go for a walk and do something.
Congratulations movie from 24:00.
Oh.
That's not what you're making.
I'll just watch it.
You're not going to watch the work, are
you?
I'm just gonna watch it.
I eat ramen, so it's fun.
I've never heard of that.
I think it would be interesting to do
that while drinking ramen or alcohol.
That's true.
And I don't like to stuff things in my
body, so I can't get up.
I'm not good at planning, so I think it
would be nice if I could decide which
one to choose and take it easy.
I see.
That's good.
Take it easy.
That's a good date.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's like that.
It's a slow feeling.
This is when I play with my friends.
Is it real?
This is important.
It's about 13 o'clock.
There is a possibility that it will be
13:30 or 14 o'clock.
That's me.
It's me all the time.
It's a slow feeling.
That's good.
I'll announce it.
My schedule is to go to the cafe at 10
o'clock.
It doesn't matter.
It's my boyfriend's birthday, so I want
to be cute, so I go to the cafe at 12
o'clock in the morning.
First of all, I will skate.
It's winter.
I will go to the cafe at 14 o'clock.
After that, I will go to the cafe.
I will buy a gift and go home at 18
o'clock.
I'm waiting for homemade cakes and
homemade dishes.
This is the point.
Homemade.
Homemade is the point.
I see.
I understand it.
It's true.
It's completely different depending on
the person.
My mom goes out a lot.
I go out, but I'm the type who comes
home late.
I'm the type who comes home early.
I understand.
who you like the best who you think is
good
You think you do it well You think you
like it 1
Ma chan
If you like it, you think it's good 2
If I like it 3
Now, I'll cast my vote
Everybody, I go to the hair salon.
I'll go to the hair salon.
I'm sorry.
Just like that.
It's cute, too.
What?
That's right.
Laugh
dazu
3, 2, 1, Time's up!
Ah, that's right! It's me, isn't it?
What? Why?
Why?
Why? Why?
I'm good at making things myself.
I'll make you a scarf.
Let's hear it.
Let's hear the reason.
Why?
I have to study.
Let's hear the reason.
By the way, what's your ranking?
You put too much ramen in it.
Why?
What was your ranking?
What was it?
3, 1, 2.
Why?
I can't do it.
Wait, wait.
It's hard to do a food fight from the
first day.
Asahi ramen?
You shouldn't put too much in it.
I thought you didn't have enough ramen.
It might be a food ramen.
You were good at making things yourself.
I knew it.
I'm good at making things myself.
You're good at making things yourself.
Okay, let's move on.
Okay.
Number 3.
Number 3 is this.
Please draw a picture of a handmade
bento that you take to a date.
Isn't this Maa-chan's design? It's a
picture.
I can do it.
This time it's a service problem.
I see.
Handmade bento to take to a date.
What is "to take to a date"?
Is it a picnic?
Isn't it like that?
It's like a picnic.
I see. It's difficult.
I can do it right away.
Take to a date.
Thank you.
Are you going on a picnic?
Do you want to change the picture of the
lunch box? Or do you want to change the
picture of the seat?
The inside of the lunch box.
What should I do?
It's done in blue.
That's fast!
Let's do it.
One, two, three!
It's so funny!
Let's make this again!
Is that just the L.O.V. of ketchup?
That's right.
No more?
If you want, we can do it at the
convenience store.
Because it takes a long time to cook.
So I want to do it as soon as possible.
That's great.
I have a lot of love for you.
I think everyone wants to eat it.
Should I put more ketchup?
I'll make the L.O.V. part thicker.
It doesn't matter.
Ketchup is important.
What is it?
Everyone wants to eat this.
Is it a lunch box?
I know it.
It's a lunch box.
I haven't eaten bento for a long time.
I haven't eaten it since high school.
It's very difficult.
What should I put in?
What's in the lunch box?
Let's go with that.
It's love, isn't it?
Love. My own love expression is love.
That's right.
All right.
I did it.
If you keep it up, you'll lose to Sora-
chan.
Please give me a point.
I'll do it, too.
Moa-chan, go ahead.
Rice, fried chicken, katsu, and
vegetables.
At first, I thought I had chosen a lunch
box, so I got a point.
I also got a point for the fried
chicken.
Men don't like katsu and fried chicken.
But if you eat it, you'll lose weight.
I see.
That's nice.
Cute.
I think I won.
No, you didn't.
I feel love.
I have a heart, too.
Love?
Me, too.
I don't know why I got a point.
Wait a minute.
Thank you for watching.
I'll make you some red bean paste.
I love red bean paste.
Why?
I made it with half-twin.
I'll make it with half-twin.
This is the point.
What's next?
I'll make it with half-twin.
I made it with half-twin.
I woke up at 5 a.m.
Actually, my mom made it.
Isn't it frozen food?
My mom made it, so it's delicious.
I'm going to eat it right away, so I'm
going to eat it right away, so I'm going
to eat it right away.
I'm going to make it again.
I'm going to put it on the fire and put
it on the fire.
I went to the hair salon at 10 a.m. and
made it.
I came to the hair salon at 5 a.m. and
What's in the lunch box?
Grilled egg?
I already put it in.
I'll show you again.
I chose this.
I'm going to open it.
I'm going to make it again.
Oh, it's big.
It's done.
It's really dirty, but I'll do it.
Ta-da.
Wow, it's really thick.
This is a meat-wrapping rice ball.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
I really like meat-wrapping rice balls.
Fried chicken.
Broccoli and tomatoes.
And fried eggs and chikuwa cucumber.
Oh, that's good.
This is a bento box that looks like a
wappa.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's really cute.
I want to eat it.
Thank you.
Okay, then.
Ruri's bento box is number one.
I'm sure this is it.
There's nothing inside.
There is.
If you like it, it's number two.
If you like me, it's number three.
Let's start voting.
Please.
Let's say the last one.
Because it's the last one.
Moa-chan, you go first.
I made a half-sweet.
I also added ramen.
It's big.
I'm going to mix it.
5,4,3,2,1
Time's up.
3, 2, 1.
Ramen is being asked.
Ramen is fine.
Why?
That's right.
1st place is me, Sora.
2nd place is Moa.
3rd place is Rinrin.
Yay!
Sora is invincible.
We are about the same.
We are different.
That's all.
Yuka, I'm proud of you.
Yay!
Let's go to the ending.
Thank you.
Let's go to the end.
This is the end.
Please look forward to it.
This tour will be held at
Jump Park.
The last block of the park will be held
at
Yokohama Bay Hall on June 22nd.
It will be held at Kanda Square Hall on
July 7th.
The contents of the park will change.
That's right.
We are in Kanto.
The costumes will also change.
Please look forward to it.
Showroom program.
We will perform at
Ja 73 Shoyakun.
The program will start at May 7th.
It will start at May 7th.
You've been waiting for
To be there on June 16th.
Keep your eyes peeled.
This time around,
there will be other practices,
do not return.
The next will be
To the place of the salute.
Please look forward to it.
Please look forward to!
I will confirm the top 5.
Thank you for the 5th place.
Thank you.
Thank you for the 4th place.
Thank you for the 3rd place.
Thank you.
Thank you for the 2nd place.
Thank you for the 1st place.
Thank you.
The next broadcast will be on June 5th,
Wednesday at 19:00.
Members will be decided.
Don't miss the next broadcast.
Please press the heart mark and
subscribe to our channel.
We also do individual broadcasts.
Please check it out.
That's all.
This is the end of the show.
See you again.
That's all.
This was Uka.
Bye-bye.
See you in the next video.